<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HealthOnTips</string>
    <string name="healthontips">HealthOnTips</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="headache">
        <h2>HEADACHE</h2>
        Now a days headache has became the part and parcle of our life(from school going kids to adults)due pollution, work pressures and tensions.
        For this we are having some tips to get rid of headache
        1) Washing face with cold water and keeping the ice bags on forehead and eyes.
        2)Hot oil massage.
        3)Meditation
        4) Listening to music.
        For those who are suffering with migraine:
        1) Dry ginger(sonti kommu) make the paste of it and apply it on the forehead we will get relief.
    </string>

    <string name="coldcommonflue">
        <h2>COLD/COMMON FLUE</h2>
        This is the most common issue that we come across in most of the situations (whether it may be summer or winter),running nose,
        blocking of nose,throat irritation,changing of voice and throat pain these are the issues we face with the cold
       1) the best cure for cold is home made khashyam
          here we are going to give recipe to prepare it
          items we need are  sonti(dry ginger),miriyalu(black pepper),daniyalu (daniya)we have to take them in equal quantities and dried and then
          we have to grain them.For one glass of water we have to use one teaspoon of the powder and we have boli it(same as we prepare tea)
          after that we have add some milk and jaggery (bellam),based on the severity we can take 1 to 2 times a day.It will give good results
          for cold ,throat pain ,throat irritation ,cough,change in voice.
        2)We can also use steamer(aviri pattadam)
          Take some hot water and add some zandu balm,turmeric and then take steam of it foe min of 15min.

       B)For small kids(below 10 years):
        1) Tulasi leaves juice is the best medicine for cold,cough and throat infection for small children.

        C)For infants(months babies):
         Babies will face nose blocks during nights(mostly), the best thing we can do get rid of this problem we can make use of Nalla Inguva.
         1)What we have to do is we have to make paste of nalla inguva then apply it on nose and throat, babies will get relief and sleeps happily.
    </string>

    <string name="asthma">
        <h2>ASTHMA</h2>
        It is also one of the common problem which we face in our daily life here we are going to give home remedy for get rid asthma problem.
         1)All we need is some onions and honey. We have grain the onions and make juice of it and add one tablespoon of honey.
          Taking it daily for one month will cure asthma.
    </string>

    <string name="stomachpain">
        <h2> STOMACH PAIN</h2>
        Mostly we will get stomach pain due to indigestion to get rid of this we have to drink more water
        other way is taking warm water.
        For small kids we have to dry the vasa koomu and make powder adding a pinch of it in milk and give them daily.
        It will improves the digestion power and also increases the capability to speak fast
    </string>

    <string name="motions">
        <h2>MOTIONS</h2>
        It is caused due to change in water and food poision,here we are going suggest a tip to get rid this
        Take small quantity of fenugreek seeds(mentulu) with curd can cure it otherwise you can also take it with water.
    </string>

    <string name="sunstroke">
        <h2>SUN STROKE</h2>
        During summer this is the main problem that everyone will face to avoid this we can have strach water(ganji water)
        with a pinch of salt and glucose.
        We can also take barley water with glucose.
        We should drink more water,coconut water,fresh fruit juice.
    </string>

    <string name="kneepain">
    <h2>KNEE PAIN</h2>
        This is the most common in adults(30+)here is a small tip that can give relief to your pain
        what we need is some fenugreek seeds(mentulu) and water.Grain the seeds and add some to it and make a paste of it.
        Apply it on the knee and keep it for half hour and after that clean it with water.
    </string>

    <string name="hairfall">
        <h2>HAIR FALL </h2>
        Now a days it is most common problem for each and everyone, the reason for this is pollution,tensions,dandruff etc
        Here we are having some home remedies to overcome this problem
        1)Make paste of fenugreek seeds and curd apply it on hair and leave it for half to one hour and wash the hair.
          For better results use twice in a week.
        2)Make the paste of hibiscus leafs and curd apply it on hair and leave it for half to one hour and wash the hair.
          For better results use twice in a week.
        3)Take olive oil,coconut oil,mustard oil mix it equal quantity and keep it on  stove and boil for 10 min  then allow
         it to cool then place the oil in one jar  and leave it undisturbed for 10 hours then use the oil.For better results use daily.
    </string>

    <string name="summertips">
        <h2>SUMMER TIPS</h2>
        During summer we have take extra care for our body to protect it from the summer effect
       1) First and the foremost thing is we have as much water as we can(min 8 lit required per day) so that we can protect our body from dehydration.
       2) Sabja (seeds) water also helps us to reduce the body heat during the summer.
       3)Fresh fruit juice will also helps to maintain the glucose content in the body.
       4)coconut water,butter milk,barley water,glucose water will help a lot .
    </string>

    <string name="vomitings">
       <h2>VOMITINGS</h2>

       1)It causes due to food poision, indigestion,water change etc to get rid of this we can take jeera power with some honey will give better results.
       2)1 spoon ginger+1/2 lemon juice take it with empty stomach will improves digestive system.
    </string>

    <string name="pimples">
        <h2>PIMPLES</h2>
        It is a most general problem that most young girls encounter.
        Here we are going to give some home remedies to over this problem.
        1)Make the paste of garlic and adding some turmeric and water to it and apply it on the pimples then clean it after 20 min.for better results use twice a week.
        2)Apply alovera gel on the pimples and leave it for 20 min and then clean it with water for better results use twice a day.
    </string>

    <string name="reelingsensation">
        <h2>REELING SENSATION</h2>
        It is mainly caused due to the usage of medicines,feeling tasteless,feel like falling down.....,
        To overcome this all we need to do is take some jeera powder with honey twice a day then you will feel better.
    </string>

    <string name="mouthulcers">
        <h2>MOUTH ULCERS</h2>
        It is caused due to the over heat in our body.To overcome this
        1)Taking sufficient smount of water is necessary.
        2)Chewing dried coconut twice a day will give the best results.
    </string>

    <string name="menstrualcramps">
        <h2>MENSTRUAL CRAMPS</h2>
        It is a general problem faced by every women.To reduce these cramps here are some remedies.
        1)Applying heat to the lower abdomen(heat bags).
        2)Massaging the lower abdomen with oil gives relief.
        3)By taking the juice of ginger,honey,lemon will give better results.
        4)Roast the sesame seeds(nuvvulu) with small amount of ghee
         after cooling it add some jaggery to this and make laddus using ghee taking one laddu a day will give best results.
    </string>

    <string name="gastericproblem">
        <h2>GASTERIC PROBLEM</h2>
        1)Take some jeera and smash it with hands(use little amount of neeru sunnam) and take it with water.
        2)Take some ginger and smash it and add it to hot water then filter it and add some amount of honey and take it .It gives the best results.
   </string>

</resources>
